Hi, in the previous lesson, we've already generated full development plan for our calculator
application and this lesson will ask a pilot to build application following this plan.
But imagine it tells us to be likely to change this plan. So we can just move our file or open it
via a copilot, or any code editor, so just do some changes. Imagine I don't like to generate tests,
I'd like to remove it and do it by myself then. So I saved my file. Currently I open it
in copilot, so it's already in context, but you can additionally move this file right here. So
if it's not, and now I can ask a pilot to create an app, create an app, follow in this plan.
And I will use engine mode, and I will click play. We'll just start building an application.
And let's see what happens. So it will help me to create a new application. So
a copilot requires an empty folder as a workspace, continue. Yeah, or we can create the workspace.
Oh, let's, let's click hello. So we now can create a new folder,
or select empty folder. So we can create new folder, just name application as calculator.
I will click create and select as empty workspace folder. So now it opens this folder.
Okay, so we'll use it as a workspace folder. We still have this plan in this chat.
I will redo-blocate this, my request, create an application, follow in this plan,
because it was close and deeper and open at the workspace.
So I think when you will use the plan mode, which will be released on, it will be much easier
to create an application. You also will need a simple prompt. I'll also share it with you.
The second, you shouldn't store your plan. You can edit it immediately in copilot.
And you shouldn't create a workspace. It will create a workspace for you. I think how it should work.
So, but we'll see. Okay, copilot already created six to those.
We can see all that to those here. You see they're almost same as in our plan.
Where is it? It's Cloud fault, create usable components, implement logic.
Constance menu of CSS here. And the next do is just verify the next steps.
So let's see. It already suggests that creates a package.json file. Do you want to
allow this ever click, allow in this session, just to allow copilot, create all the files without my confirmation.
And if you create file by file, we will see the whole application, I guess in a minute,
we have the test config file. So it means it follows the TypeScript configuration.
We have width config is a bundle which helps us to create the projects.
It already creates a source folder with a main file where we will create a container for our
application inside of the DOM. So let's wait. We have index.css. You see it created step-by-step.
We have the styles for all the bottom types. It already created application file. You see,
we have the display and keypad. We also store all the buttons inside of the Constance.
It should add, I guess, more components because we still need to have the card.
We have the Constance already the buttons as we describe. In our plan, we have types,
types is for calculator and with the button what props it might have.
We also have the components, the display component, our with display it,
as the card component,
here's a key button, it creates it step-by-step.
Okay, we have the keypad,
and display different buttons as always, wait a bit.
So now it was created the hook,
where is the hook, your calculator. So this hook, what it does, it helps to clear all the values
to use the backspace. So it provides the functions for all the buttons. It can help handle
different buttons. Okay, it's fine, it also contains the calculate function.
Okay, I like it. We have also the Redmi.md, we use all the project setup.
Okay, nice. There is some description of what photos we have,
how to install and run application.
Oh, okay, that's fine.
Yeah, this is some improvements. Okay, since you finished,
he mentioned just all the files was created, all the components, etc.
He mentioned how to run this project. So we need to open the terminal right here.
We already in our workspace folder,
but we just can copy paste this to commands to install all the dependencies and run the project.
Okay, we can open it.
So I will close all my tabs. So we have an application with the calculator,
no worries to dark, you will fix it in the next lessons, just main go, check it works.
Be nice.
Okay, is it work?
Yes, it works. Okay. Yeah, of course, there are some
moments that if we start typing something, you will be just adding you a legit
yeah, but normally it works.
Okay, okay. Oh, looks good, I guess. So it's the next lesson.
We will fix all the mistakes, all the logic, make it beautiful, we'll add unit tests, might be
improved on documentation and etc. I will see you in the next lesson.